<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Engineering Projects &amp; Academic Experiences on Andrew&#39;s Website</title>
    <link>https://andrewjohnwhitaker.com/academics-engineering/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Engineering Projects &amp; Academic Experiences on Andrew&#39;s Website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 00:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://andrewjohnwhitaker.com/academics-engineering/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Silent Solutions EMC Course</title>
      <link>https://andrewjohnwhitaker.com/academics-engineering/silentsolutions/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 00:12:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrewjohnwhitaker.com/academics-engineering/silentsolutions/</guid>
      <description>Applying Practical EMI Design &amp;amp; Troubleshooting Techniques December 15-16, 2021 I had the pleasure of attending a synchronized video session of Silent Solutions&#39; EMI/EMC crash course, presented by Lee Hill. This course took place over two very busy and informational days, and although the course is usually held in person, the remote version included all material and demonstrations!
I would highly recommend taking this class yourself if this is a topic relevant or interesting to you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hand-Building Electric Guitars</title>
      <link>https://andrewjohnwhitaker.com/academics-engineering/customguitars/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2021 19:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrewjohnwhitaker.com/academics-engineering/customguitars/</guid>
      <description>Intro One of my first experiences with soldering and workbench troubleshooting skills came from an electric guitar I received in middle school. A great deal discovered on Craigslist by my father and uncle, it was an intermediate model with a number of upgrades available on guitars five times its price. However, something was never quite right about how it sounded, and my playing wasn&amp;rsquo;t the sole offender.
Fast-forward to one day during my senior year of high school, when I plugged the guitar in only to get nothing out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wireless Audio Control Interface - WACI</title>
      <link>https://andrewjohnwhitaker.com/academics-engineering/waci/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2019 00:12:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrewjohnwhitaker.com/academics-engineering/waci/</guid>
      <description>Please note that you may be prompted to download .pdf files if you are on a mobile device.
This project was designed and assembled at Northeastern University in the fall of 2019 for my team&amp;rsquo;s EECE senior capstone design project. Included here is the abstract and associated project materials. Thanks to group members Joshua Berlin, Jess Bardio, Matan Silver, Phil Del Signore, and Lousia Beckwith as well as our advisor, Professor Bahram Shafai.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
